

NASSER FAQIRI

→ JUNIOR → JAVA DEVELOPER

Located in Brussels
NasserFaqiri@hotmail.com
+32 477 65 12 20
CosmosDesign.be
Driving License B



EDUCATIE

STUDENT / 2021 - 2022 Java EE - Intec Brussel

SECONDARY DIPLOMA / 2016 Electro Auto Mechanics Business management



WORK EXPERIENCE

CC WILRIJK (AUG 2018 - MAR 2022) Database update ADAS system recalibration Tesla vehicle repair

COSMOS DESIGN (APR 2016 - NOV 2018) Website design Graphic design



LANGUAGES

DutchPerfectly spoken/writtenEnglishPerfectly spoken/writtenFrenchWell spoken/writtenPersianMother tongue



PROFILE

Goal-oriented Junior Java Developer with 1+ years of experience. I am a driven professional with a broad technical skillset. Committed to continuously expanding knowledge, always willing to search for new ones techniques and design patterns to better solve a problem. As a team player, I do not only take into account the interests of the customer, but also those of my colleagues and managers.



PERSONAL SKILLS

FRONT-END

- Website development: E-Commerce, Creative Content
- · Social media marketing
- · All platform friendly websites
- · Brand awareness

Wordpress

HTML

JavaScript

UX/UI

CSS

BACK-END

- Develop creative solutions for complex problems
- · Good understanding of databases: Oracle, Maven, MySQL, Spring
- Software development Java
- Investigate configurations and implement better solutions